# **ANTONIA STIPIĆ**

CHILDCARE PROVIDER

#### **DETAILS**

antonis.stipic@gmail.com www.nannyberlin.com

#### SKILLS

De-escalating interpersonal conflict with patience and effective communication skills

Mindfulness and and listening skills

Compassionate and friendly interpersonal skills

Flexibility and calmness

Planning, logistics and organization skills

#### LANGUAGES

Croatian C2
English C1
Italian B1
Spanish A2
German A1

#### HOBBIES

Swimming, sailing, cycling, volunteering, hiking, writing, photography

#### **PROFILE**

I am a childcare provider with a multi-disciplinary education background and an interest in working as a childcare provider in the Berlin metropolitan area. I believe that every child has huge potential and I enjoy working with them to overcome challenges. I have had rewarding experiences working with children with physical and developmental disabilities. I have witnessed positive growth and transformations in children I have worked with; I would like to think that my work practicing respect, good communication and hard work - was part of those positive changes.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Nanny

Berlin | Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

Served as full-time nanny for a 2-year old. Provided in-home care. Occasional help with 8 year old sister.
Reference available upon request.

#### Au pair

Ireland | Oct 2016 - Jul 2017

Provided supervision and home care for the basic needs of 4 boys, between the ages of 3-10, including one child with autism.

Prepared meals, created activity schedules that allowed the children to learn more about the world and develop their interests; helped with homework and classwork, and maintained and cleaned domestic spaces.

Reference available upon request.

## Co-founder, NGO "Prijatelj"

Split, Croatia | 2013 - 2015

Organizing various activities for families and youth in the community, including family playdays in Marjan forest park.

Developed resources to foster accessibility of cafés, clubs, and

Developed materials and campaign to promote awareness about internet addictions.

Visit website: <u>http://www.udruga-prijatelj.net</u>

restaurants for youth with disabilities.

# Teacher assistant, Primary school "Mertojak"

Split, Croatia | Sep 2013 - Dec 2013

Assisted classroom teacher in classroom with group of 4 autistic boys on classroom preparation.

Everyday activities working with small groups of students to enhance learning processes.

Keeping classrooms safe and tidy.

# Volunteer, Family Centre of Split-Dalmatia County (government institution)

Split, Croatia | Jan 2012 - Dec 2012

Volunteering with children with learning difficulties.

2-4 hours weekly work with primary school kids (6-12 years old). approx. 10 children included.

Focus interviews with parents about learning habits of their children

Presentation of projects in media, tv interviews

Visit website: <a href="https://czss-split.hr/">https://czss-split.hr/</a>

# Lecturer, Civil society organization "Gong"

Split, Croatia | 2008 - 2009

Conducted youth outreach educational workshops on topics including 'Youth on the Labour Market' and 'Local Governance in Croatia.'

#### **EDUCATION**

# M.A., Maritime studies, University of Split

Split | 2002 - 2007

# Language grammar high school

Split | 1998 - 2002